

SeYeong Im

CONTROL LOGIC ENGINEER · FIRMWARE ENGINEE

110, Seochojungang-ro, Seocho-gu, Seoul, Republic of Korea

□ (+82) 10-9101-7563 | **S** syl1219ss@naver.com

"We see as much as we know."

Summary.

I'm Seyeong Im, who want to become Control Logic Engineer. My research interests is Control theory. I think that undergraduate course(4 years) is too short to learn about control. So I want to study this field more after graduating university.

I hope to know more and see more.

Research Interest

Control Theory Robust Control, Disturbance Observer...

Motor Control DC, BLDC, PMSM

Education

KwangWoon University

Seoul, S.Korea
Mar. 2016 - Feb. 2023(Expected)

B.S. IN SCHOOL OF ROBOTICS

• Total GPA: 4.38/4.50 Major GPA: 4.42/4.50

• Club: BARAM(Robotics Academic Group) - [2021 Club director of Planning]

Work Experience _____

MRL(Magnetic Robotics Lab, Kwangwoon University)

Seoul, S.Korea

STUDENT RESEARCHER

Jan. 2021 - present

- Research on Magnetic navigation system
- Research on Magnetic capsule robot control in human gastrointestinal tract & blood vessel
- Research on Permanent magnet localization

Kwangwoon University

Seoul, S.Korea
Mar. 2021 - Dec. 2021

TEACHING ASSISTANT

- engineering mathematics 1
- electromagnetics 1
- circuit theory 1
- · circuit theory 2

Skills____

Programming C/C++, Matlab

Tool Solidworks, Inventor, Pspice, AVR, IAR, Altair Flux, MPLAB

Languages Korean, English, Japanese

Publication

INTERNATIONAL JOURNAL

Electrical Optimization Method Based on a Novel Arrangement of the Magnetic Navigation System

2022.07 with Gradient and Uniform Saddle Coils,

Sensors

Sungjun Kim, Mingyu Cho, Seyeong Im, Yunjoong Ho and Jaekwang Nam

DOMESTIC CONFERENCE

Control of Human Interaction-Based Wheelchair Simulator System's Slope Using Disturbance

2022.06 **Observer**, ICROS 2022

Seyeong Im, Chanhyuk Kim, Hoseok Lee, Sungjun Kim and Juhoon Back

AUGUST 9, 2022 SEYEONG IM · CURRICULUM VITAE

Honors & Awards

AWARDS

2022.05	Dean's List , Academic Excellence Award	Seoul, S.Korea
HONORS		
2016.08	Half tuition Scholarship, Academic Excellence Schloarship	Seoul, S.Korea
2017.02	Half tuition Scholarship, Academic Excellence Schloarship	Seoul, S.Korea
2020.08	Half tuition Scholarship, Academic Excellence Schloarship	Seoul, S.Korea
2021.02	Quarter tuition Scholarship, Academic Excellence Schloarship	Seoul, S.Korea
2021.08	Half tuition Scholarship, Academic Excellence Schloarship	Seoul, S.Korea
2022.02	Half tuition Scholarship, Academic Excellence Schloarship	Seoul, S.Korea

Projects _____

Two Wheel Balancing Robot

Seoul, S.Korea

Seoul, S.Korea

Personal Project Aug. 2020 - Nov. 2020

• The goal of this project is to know what is control

2021.10 Dean's List, Academic Excellence Award

- To get Robot's state(degree, angular velocity), i used encoder and IMU
- Using cascade pd(pos), pi(angular velocity)

Micro Robot Control In Human Blood Vessel

Seoul, S.Korea

MRL Project Jan. 2021 - Jun. 2021

- A magnetic navigation system (MNS) for the wireless manipulation of micro-robots in human blood vessels is a possible surgical tool for coronary artery disease
- To generate uniform magnetic field & gradient, MNS composed of one conventional pair of Maxwell and Helmholtz coils and one newly developed pair of gradient and uniform saddle coils
- In the MNS, the microrobot can move with 5 degrees of freedom.

Sensor analysis & filtering Seoul, S.Korea

Personal Project Mar. 2021 - Jun. 2021

- The goal of this project is to know filters and frequency analysis
- To apply filters, I analyzed the frequency of sensors's output
- · Using First Order RC Filter, MAF, IIR, FIR, kalman

Maxon DCX35L Motor Control

Seoul, S.Korea

Personal Project Oct. 2021 - Dec. 2021

- Simulation (simulink&ode) and applied to real motors
- Using cascade pd(pos), pi(angular velocity), pi(current)
- As the system operates in simulation(ode), the real system operates

Position Control of SPMSM Using LQR & Full-order Estimator

Seoul, S.Korea Nov. 2021 - Dec. 2021

• Simulation project using matlab, simulink

- To use LQR, linearized the SPMSM's system mtx(nonlinear mtx)
- Using full-order estimator, to get states
- Verified using MCLV-2 Development Board

Development of Magnetic navigation System(MNS) and & Control method

Seoul, S.Korea

MRL Project Jul. 2021 - Present

Project in preparation for paper(1st author)

- Miniaturized MNS by using a scalar robot and a C-type electromagnet to replace the existing large and heavy MNS
- Using FEM analysis to create a system that generates the maximum magnetic field within limited conditions (maximum output of the power supply and payload of the robot)
- To reduce eddy current loss, Manufactured by stacking 30PNF1600 from POSCO
- To compensate design & measurement error, using DOB(disturbance observer)

Wheelchair Simulator Seoul, S. Korea

CAPSTONE PROJECT

Jan. 2022 - jun.2022

• We realize real track in VR

- Realize gravity's load using force control
- To realize track's slope, we control system's degree using DOB(disturbance observer)& fuzzy PID

August 9, 2022 SeYeong Im · Curriculum vitae 2